#### Sign In

    * 
    * 
    * Remember me Not recommended on shared computers
        
    * Sign In

* **Privacy Policy**
    
    CreativeClash is committed to protecting and respecting your privacy. We collect only the personal information that we need from you to operate our website, and we do not divulge your personal information to anyone else unless we are ordered to do so by a court that has jurisdiction over us.
    
    #### What information we hold about you
    
    If you register an account with CreativeClash, we collect and process the following personal data:
    
    1. Your email address.
        
    2. The profile fields on your account with us.
        
    3. Any content that you have uploaded.

    **Whether or not you register for an account, we collect the following information:**
    
    1. Your IP address.
        
    2. Any information that you send through our contact form.
        
    3. Cookies that are read from your web browser. See "Cookie policy" below.

    #### How your personal information is used
    
    We may use your personal information in the following ways:
    
    1. To enable you to browse and contribute content to this site.
        
    2. We may use your email address to inform you of activity on our site.
        
    3. Your IP address is recorded when you perform certain actions on our site. Your IP address is never publicly visible.

    We may collect non-personally identifiable information about you in the course of your interaction with our site. This information may include technical information about the browser or type of device you're using. This information will be used purely for the purposes of analytics and tracking the number of visitors to our site.
    
    #### Cookie policy
    
    Cookies are small text files which are set by us on your computer which allow us to provide certain functionality on our site, such as being able to log in, or remembering certain preferences. We do not use cookies for marketing purposes, nor do we currently partner with any third parties who set cookies. You will be offered the option to opt-out of our use of cookies when browsing our website, however refusal may impair site functionality. 
    
    #### Your rights
    
    You have a right to access the personal data we hold about you, to obtain a copy of it, or to request its erasure. Please contact us if this applies to you. You can also contact us if you believe that the information we hold for you is incomplete or inaccurate.
    
    #### Changes to this policy
    
    These terms may be changed at any time without notice. They were last updated on September 1, 2022.

#### Event information

#### Links

#### You are responsible for your own viewing experience while using this website. We have endeavored to provide as many means as possible for you to curate your experience here.

* [IPS Theme](https://www.ipsfocus.com/) by [IPSFocus](https://www.ipsfocus.com/)
    *  Light Mode
        
    *  Dark Theme (Default)

* Create New...

 Change theme
